Guide to the Time Inc. Annex Files 1854, 1909, 1923-2014 MS 3009-RG 39
New-York Historical Society
- Magazine Development: 1965: Travel Magazines (Offsite-box 3915, Folder 25)
- Magazine Development: 1966: International Publishing, 1962-1966 (Offsite-box 3915, Folder 26)
- Magazine Development: 1966: Magazine About the Future (Offsite-box 3916, Folder 1)
- Magazine Development: 1966: Magazine for Subway Riders (Offsite-box 3916, Folder 2)
- Magazine Development: 1966: Time in Japanese (Offsite-box 3916, Folder 3)
- Magazine Development: 1966: Time in Spanish (Offsite-box 3916, Folder 4)
- Magazine Development: 1967: International Publishing: British Life (Offsite-box 3916, Folder 5)
- Magazine Development: 1967: International Publishing: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3916, Folder 7)
- Magazine Development: 1967: The Student (Offsite-box 3916, Folder 8)
- Magazine Development: 1967: Time in French, 1967, 1974 (Offsite-box 3916, Folder 9-10)
- Magazine Development: 1967: Time in German (Offsite-box 3916, Folder 11-12)
- Magazine Development: 1967: You Personally (Offsite-box 3916, Folder 13)
- Magazine Development: 1968: International Publishing: British Life in Japanese, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 3916, Folder 14)
- Magazine Development: 1968: The Movies Proposal by Thomas Thompson (Offsite-box 3916, Folder 15)
- Magazine Development: 1968: Television Preview (Offsite-box 3916, Folder 16)
- Magazine Development: 1968-1969: Art Magazines, 1967-1969 (Offsite-box 3916, Folder 17)
- Magazine Development: 1969 and Before: Woman's Day, 1958, 1969 (Offsite-box 3916, Folder 18)
- Magazine Development: 1969: Life Supplements: Louis Harris Story (Offsite-box 3916, Folder 19-21)
- Magazine Development: 1969: Magazine for Blacks, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 3917, Folder 1)
- Magazine Development: 1969: On View, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 3917, Folder 2)
- Magazine Development: 1969: Topic, 1969, undated (Offsite-box 3917, Folder 3)
- Magazine Development: 1969-1970: Life Supplements: Children's Magazine, 1969, undated (Offsite-box 3917, Folder 4)
- Magazine Development: 1969-1970: Supplements: Food, 1968-1970 (Offsite-box 3917, Folder 5)
- Magazine Development: 1969-1970: Supplements: Health, undated (Offsite-box 3917, Folder 6)
- Magazine Development: 1969-1970: Life Supplement: Movies and TV, undated (Offsite-box 4044, Folder 14)
- Magazine Development: 1969-1970: Life Supplements [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R70)
- Magazine Development: 1943 (?): Arts of Living, 1931 (Offsite-box 4029, Folder 3)
- Magazine Development: 1946: Time for the Blind (Offsite-box 4029, Folder 4)
- Magazine Development: 1948: Proposed Intellectual Magazine (Offsite-box 4029, Folder 5)
- Magazine Development: 1967: International Editions, 1967, undated (Offsite-box 4031, Folder 6)
- Magazine Development: 1969-1970: Life Supplement: Money (Offsite-box 3917, Folder 7)
- Magazine Development: 1969-1970: Life Supplements: Movies and Television, 1968-1970, undated (Offsite-box 3917, Folder 8)
- Magazine Development: 1969-1970: Life Supplements: Travel, undated (Offsite-box 3917, Folder 9)
- Magazine Development: 1969-1970: Life Supplements: Miscellaneous, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 3917, Folder 10)
- Magazine Development: 1970: Environment (Offsite-box 3917, Folder 11)
- Magazine Development: 1970: Sunday Magazines, 1970-1975 (Offsite-box 3917, Folder 12)
- Magazine Development: 1971: Business and Law (Offsite-box 3917, Folder 13)
- Magazine Development: 1971: Camera Month (Offsite-box 3917, Folder 14)
- Magazine Development: 1971: Camera Month, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 4029, Folder 6)
- Magazine Development: 1971: Camera Month, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 4030, Folder 1-2)
- Magazine Development: 1971: View (Offsite-box 4030, Folder 3-5)
- Magazine Development: 1971: View (Offsite-box 4031, Folder 1)
- Magazine Development: 1971: Well (Offsite-box 4031, Folder 2-4)
- Magazine Development: 1971: Well (Offsite-box 3917, Folder 15-16)
- Magazine Development: 1971: Well Circulation Promotion, 1972-1976 (Offsite-box 3917, Folder 17)
- Magazine Development: 1971: Well Revised Prospectus (Offsite-box 3917, Folder 18)
- Magazine Development: 1971: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3917, Folder 19)
- Magazine Development: 1972: Camera Month, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 3917, Folder 20-21)
- Magazine Development: 1972: Camera Month: Direct Mail, undated (Offsite-box 3917, Folder 22-23)
- Magazine Development: 1972: View: Direct Mail, undated (Offsite-box 3917, Folder 24)
- Magazine Development: 1972: View: Dummies, undated (Offsite-box 3917, Folder 25)
- Magazine Development: 1972: View: Dummies, undated (Offsite-box 3918, Folder 1)
- Magazine Development: 1972: View: Miscellaneous, 1971-1973 (Offsite-box 3918, Folder 2-5)
- Magazine Development: 1972: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3918, Folder 6)
- Magazine Development: 1973: Camera Month: Dummies, undated (Offsite-box 3918, Folder 7-9)
- Magazine Development: 1973: Camera Month: Miscellaneous: January and February (Offsite-box 3918, Folder 10)
- Magazine Development: 1973: Camera Month: Miscellaneous: March and December, 1973-1974, undated (Offsite-box 3918, Folder 11)
- Magazine Development: 1973: Magazine for Blacks (Offsite-box 3918, Folder 12)
- Magazine Development: 1973: Magazine of Religion and Ethics (Offsite-box 3918, Folder 13)
- Magazine Development: 1973: Zoom (Offsite-box 3918, Folder 14)
- Magazine Development: 1974: City Magazines, 1968-1974 (Offsite-box 3918, Folder 15)
- Magazine Development: 1974 (?): i (Offsite-box 4031, Folder 5)
- Magazine Development: 1974: Science Illustrated (Offsite-box 3918, Folder 16)
- Magazine Development: 1975: American Express Newsletter (Offsite-box 3918, Folder 17)
- Magazine Development: 1975-1976: People International Syndication (Offsite-box 3918, Folder 18)
- Magazine Development: 1976 and Before: Woman: Edit, 1974-1976 (Offsite-box 3918, Folder 19-21)
- Magazine Development: 1976 and Before: Woman: Edit [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R70)
- Magazine Development: 1976 and Before: Woman: Miscellaneous, 1972-1976 (Offsite-box 3918, Folder 22)
- Magazine Development: 1976 and Before: Woman: Miscellaneous, 1972-1976 (Offsite-box 3919, Folder 1)
- Magazine Development: 1976 and Before: Woman: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Offsite-box R70)
- Magazine Development: 1976: New York World Times (Offsite-box 3919, Folder 2)
- Magazine Development: 1976: Reading Habits Study (Robert Ellis), 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 3919, Folder 3)
- Magazine Development: 1976: Sunbelt (Offsite-box 3919, Folder 4)
- Magazine Development: 1976: Surveys and Studies: Television and Its Impact on Magazines (Offsite-box 3919, Folder 5)
- Magazine Development: 1976: Surveys and Studies Television and Its Impact on Magazines [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R70)
- Magazine Development: 1976: Woman: Advertising, 1976, undated (Offsite-box 3919, Folder 6)
- Magazine Development: 1976: Woman: Market Research-Focus Groups, 1976-1977, undated (Offsite-box 3919, Folder 7)
- Magazine Development: 1976: Woman: Market Research: Kelso Sutton (Offsite-box 3919, Folder 8)
- Magazine Development: 1976: Woman: Market Research: Miscellaneous, 1974-1976 (Offsite-box 3919, Folder 9)
- Magazine Development: 1977 and Before: Home Box Office (HBO) Guide, 1975-1977, undated (Offsite-box 3919, Folder 10)
- Magazine Development: 1977: Enjoy, 1977, undated (Offsite-box 3919, Folder 11)
- Magazine Development: 1977: Oldsters, 1976-1977, undated (Offsite-box 3919, Folder 12)
- Magazine Development: 1977: The Road, 1977, undated (Offsite-box 3919, Folder 13)
- Magazine Development: 1977: The Road [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R70)
- Magazine Development: 1977: Travel (Offsite-box 3919, Folder 14)
- Magazine Development: 1977: Woman: Advertising, 1977, undated (Offsite-box 3919, Folder 15)
- Magazine Development: 1977: Woman: Circulation, 1976-1977, undated (Offsite-box 3919, Folder 16)
- Magazine Development: 1977: Woman: 11/14/77 Dummy Layout Sheets (Offsite-box 3919, Folder 17)
- Magazine Development: 1977: Woman: 1/77 Dummies (Offsite-box 3919, Folder 18)
- Magazine Development: 1977: Woman: Dummies - 8/77 and 11/77 (Printed) (Offsite-box 3920, Folder 1-3)
- Magazine Development: 1977: Woman: Dummies (Unused) (Offsite-box 3920, Folder 4-5)
- Magazine Development: 1977: Woman: Edit, 1977-1978, undated (Offsite-box 3920, Folder 6-7)
- Magazine Development: 1977: Woman: Financial, 1976-1977, undated (Offsite-box 3920, Folder 8-9)
- Magazine Development: 1977: Woman: Legal, 1976-1978 (Offsite-box 3920, Folder 10-11)
- Magazine Development: 1977: Woman Legal [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R70)
- Magazine Development: 1977: Woman: Critiques, 1976-1977, undated (Offsite-box 3920, Folder 12)
- Magazine Development: 1977: Woman: Market Research: Focus Group (Offsite-box 3920, Folder 13)
- Magazine Development: 1977: Woman: Market Research: Focus Group (Offsite-box 3921, Folder 1)
- Magazine Development: 1977: Woman: Market Research: Vopan (Offsite-box 3921, Folder 2)
- Magazine Development: 1977: Woman: Market Research: Miscellaneous (#1) (Offsite-box 3921, Folder 3-4)
- Magazine Development: 1977: Woman: Market Research: Miscellaneous (#2), 1977, undated (Offsite-box 3921, Folder 5-6)
- Magazine Development: 1977: Woman: Market Research: Miscellaneous (#3), 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3921, Folder 7)
- Magazine Development: 1977: Woman: Production, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 3921, Folder 8-9)
- Magazine Development: 1977: Woman: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3921, Folder 10)
- Magazine Development: 1978: Woman (Offsite-box 3921, Folder 11)
- Magazine Development: 1979: Miscellaneous, 1978 (Offsite-box 3921, Folder 12)
- Magazine Development: 1980: Missing Persons Outside Proposal (Offsite-box 3921, Folder 13)
- Magazine Development: 1981: New Florida (Proposal to Buy) (Offsite-box 3921, Folder 14)
- Magazine Development: 1981: People: Book: Outside Proposals [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R70)
- Magazine Development: 1981: Various Letters with Brief Proposals Not Pursued from Auckerman, McCormick, Persky, Schneider, Will (Offsite-box 3921, Folder 15)
- Magazine Development: 1981: Various Letters with Brief Proposals Not Pursued from Aukerman, McCormick, Persky, Schneider, Will [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R70)
- Magazine Development: 1981: Various Proposals [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R70)
- Magazine Development: 1981-1982: Together (Offsite-box 3921, Folder 16-17)
- Magazine Development: 1982: City/Regional Magazines Strategy and Various Proposals (Offsite-box 3921, Folder 18)
- Magazine Development: 1982: New: Kent Smith's Proposal and Prospectus (Offsite-box 3921, Folder 19)
- Magazine Development: 1982: Quality Competitive Analysis (Offsite-box 3921, Folder 20)
- Magazine Development: 1982: Together Prospectus (Offsite-box 3921, Folder 21)
- Magazine Development: 1982: US Punch (A Humor Magazine) (Offsite-box 3921, Folder 22)
- Magazine Development: 1982: Various Proposals (Offsite-box 3921, Folder 23)
- Magazine Development: 1982: Various Proposals [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R70)
- Magazine Development: 1982: Weekend (Proposal by Malcom Carter) (Offsite-box 3921, Folder 24)
- Magazine Development: 1983: World Business Digest (Offsite-box 3921, Folder 25)
- Magazine Development: 1982: Yes! Magazine (Offsite-box 3921, Folder 26)
- Magazine Development: 1981-83: Washington Weekly, 1981-1983 (Offsite-box 3922, Folder 1-2)
- Magazine Development: 1982-1983: Quality: Miscellaneous, 1981-1987 (Offsite-box 3922, Folder 3)
- Magazine Development: 1983: Computer Research into Violability; Memo About Possible Acquisitions; Proposals from Chuck Martin (Offsite-box 3922, Folder 4)
- Magazine Development: 1983: Power/Lipton (Offsite-box 3922, Folder 5)
- Magazine Development: 1983: Power/Lipton [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R70)
- Magazine Development: 1983: Together: RMH Market Research and Color Evaluation (Offsite-box 3922, Folder 6)
- Magazine Development: 1983: Together: Dummy (Offsite-box 3922, Folder 7)
- Magazine Development: 1983: Various Proposals (Offsite-box 3922, Folder 8)
- Magazine Development: 1983: Various Proposals [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R70)
- Magazine Development: 1983-1984, 1983, undated (Offsite-box 3922, Folder 9-10)
- Magazine Development: 1983-1984: Together [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R70)
- Magazine Development: 1984: Advance: Manuscripts [empty], undated (Offsite-box 3922, Folder 11)
- Magazine Development: 1984: Advance: Prospectus, undated (Offsite-box 3922, Folder 12)
- Magazine Development: 1984: Advance: Miscellaneous, 1984, undated (Offsite-box 3922, Folder 13-14)
- Magazine Development: 1984: Advance Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Offsite-box R70)
- Magazine Development: 1984: May 14-20 Investment Week Volume 1 Number 1 (Offsite-box 3922, Folder 15)
- Magazine Development: 1984: Religion/Ethics Various Proposals (Offsite-box 3922, Folder 16)
- Magazine Development: 1984: Scholastic Inc. Preliminary Review of Company (For Possible Acquisition?) (Offsite-box 3922, Folder 17)
- Magazine Development: 1984: Sports international Proposal by Non-Time Incers (Offsite-box 3922, Folder 18)
- Magazine Development: 1984: Various Proposals and Titles (Offsite-box 3922, Folder 19)
- Magazine Development: 1984: Woman Weekly: Editorial Prospectus by Judith Daniels (Offsite-box 3922, Folder 20)
- Magazine Development: 1984: Woman Weekly: Report: "Reviewing the Effect of Size on the Economics for a Woman's Weekly" (Offsite-box 3922, Folder 21)
- Magazine Development: 1984: Various Proposals (Offsite-box 3922, Folder 22)
- Magazine Development: 1983-85 Woman (aka Flash): Miscellaneous, 1977, 1983-1986, undated (Offsite-box 3922, Folder 23)
- Magazine Development: 1984/5: Advance: Market Research, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 3922, Folder 24)
- Magazine Development: 1985: Advance: Dummy Plans, undated (Offsite-box 3922, Folder 25-26)
- Magazine Development: 1985: Advance: Miscellaneous Including Resumes (Offsite-box 3923, Folder 1)
- Magazine Development: 1985: Family: Prospectus, circa July 1985? Gaines Arguments for Same (Offsite-box 3923, Folder 2)
- Magazine Development: 1985: Skunkworks (For Developing Smaller Circulation Titles Including Joint Ventures) (Offsite-box 3923, Folder 3)
- Magazine Development: 1985-1986: Home Office: Test Issues [empty], undated (Offsite-box 3923, Folder 4)
- Magazine Development: 1985-1986: Home Office: Miscellaneous, 1985-1987, undated (Offsite-box 3923, Folder 5)
- Magazine Development: 1985-1986: Picture Week (Offsite-box 3923, Folder 6)
- Magazine Development: 1986 You: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3923, Folder 7)
- Magazine Development: 1986-1987: Leisure: Test Issues (Offsite-box 3923, Folder 8-9)
- Magazine Development: 1986-1987: Leisure: Miscellaneous, 1986, undated (Offsite-box 3923, Folder 10-11)
- Magazine Development: 1986-1987: Quality: Miscellaneous, 1983-1987 (Offsite-box 3923, Folder 12)
- Magazine Development: 1986-1987: Quality Test Issue (Offsite-box 3923, Folder 13)
- Magazine Development: 1986-1987: Real Estate: Dummy and Test Issues, 1985, undated (Offsite-box 3923, Folder 14-15)
- Magazine Development: 1992: Miscellaneous, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 3923, Folder 16)
- Magazine Development: 1994: Mouth2Mouth Test Issues (Offsite-box 3923, Folder 17)
- Magazine Development: 1995-1996: Your Future First Issue (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 1)
- Magazine Group: Advertising Promotion: Space and Home Advertisements "American Renewal", 1981 (Offsite-box 4032, Folder 1)
- Magazine Group: Surveys and Studies: 1969?: Comparing the Performance of Magazines and Television, undated (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 2)
- Magazine Group: Surveys and Studies: 1975: Advertisers and Agencies Rate Time Inc. Publications (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 3)
- Magazine Group: Surveys and Studies: 1975: Magazine Purchasing Methods (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 4)
- Magazine Group; Surveys and Studies: 1975: Readership of Ten Magazines (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 5)
- Magazine Group: Surveys and Studies: 1975: Time. Inc. Readers' Habits (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 6)
- Maps, undated (Offsite-box 4032, Folder 2)
- The March of Time!, 1937, 1975 (Offsite-box 4007, Folder 10)
  1 audiotape reel: analog, 5 in., 1/4 in tape. Label on container: "The March of Time!" 1937 31, Oct. 1975"
- The March of Time: Alien Property Custodian [RESTRICTED], 1942-1944 (Offsite-box R70)
- The March of Time Commercial: American Association of Advertising Agencies (AAAA) Gag Real, 1938 (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 7)
- The March of Time: Commercial: American Association of Advertising Agencies (AAAA) and Association of National Advertisers (ANA): America and Advertising, 1941, undated (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 8)
- The March of Time: Commercial: American Association of Advertising Agencies (AAAA) and Association of National Advertisers (ANA): Freedom is Indivisible (Eisenhower), 1948-1949, undated (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 9)
- The March of Time: Commercial: American Association of Advertising Agencies (AAAA) and Association of National Advertisers (ANA): Freedom is Indivisible (Eisenhower) [RESTRICTED], 1948 (Offsite-box R70)
- The March of Time: Commercial: American Grocery Manufacturers Association (AGMA), 1939 (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 10)
- The March of Time: Commercial: American Red Cross: A Life in Your Hands, 1947-1950 (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 11)
- The March of Time: Commercial: American Red Cross: A Life in Your Hands [RESTRICTED], 1948 (Offsite-box R70)
- The March of Time: Commercial: American Red Cross: All Together, 1948 (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 12)
- The March of Time: Commercial: American Red Cross: All Together [RESTRICTED], 1948 (Offsite-box R70)
- The March of Time: Commercial: American Red Cross: At His Side, 1943-1944 (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 13)
- The March of Time: Commercial: American Red Cross: Call to Action, 1945-1946 (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 14)
- The March of Time: Commercial: American Red Cross: The Job Ahead [RESTRICTED], 1946 (Offsite-box R70)
- The March of Time: Commercial: American Red Cross: Seeing Them Through, 1944-1945 (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 15)
- The March of Time: Commercial: American Red Cross: Since Pearl Harbor, 1943 (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 16)
- The March of Time: Commercial: American Red Cross: Since Pearl Harbor [RESTRICTED], 1943 (Offsite-box R70)
- The March of Time: Commercial: American Red Cross: Your Red Cross [RESTRICTED], 1954 (Offsite-box R70)
- The March of Time Commercial: American Red Cross, 1951-1954 (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 17)
- The March of Time Commercial: Association of National Advertisers (ANA): Gag Reels, 1937, undated (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 18)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Association of National Advertisers (ANA): Out of Today a Better Tomorrow, 1943-1944, undated (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 19)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Association of National Advertisers (ANA): Out of Today a Better Tomorrow [RESTRICTED], 1941-1943 (Offsite-box R70)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Association of National Advertisers (ANA): Science in Business, 1939-1940, undated (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 20)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Association of National Advertisers (ANA): Science in Business [RESTRICTED], 1939 (Offsite-box R70)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Association of National Advertisers (ANA): Year of Decision, 1945-1946, undated (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 21)
- The March of Time: Commercial: American Telegraph and Telephone (AT&T): Vote of Confidence, 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 22)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Auto Accessories, 1939-1940 (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 23)
- The March of Time: Commercial: A-Miscellaneous, 1946-1951 (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 24)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Bank of America: California Heritage: [RESTRICTED], 1953 (Offsite-box R70)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Bank of America: California Heritage: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1953 (Offsite-box R70)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Bank of America: California Heritage: Long Version, 1952-1953, undated (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 25)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Bank of America: California Heritage: Miscellaneous, 1951-1953, undated (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 26)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Bank of America: California Heritage: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED]], 1951-1952 (Offsite-box R70)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Bank of America: California Heritage: Short Version, 1953 (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 27)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Bank of America: Miscellaneous, 1947-1953 (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 28)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Bank of America: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1948 (Offsite-box R70)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Bank of America: New California [RESTRICTED], 1949 (Offsite-box R70)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Bank of America: New California: Legal, 1948-1949 (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 29)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Bank of America: New California: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1948-1949, undated (Offsite-box R70)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Bank of America: New California: Long Version, 1948 (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 30)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Bank of America: New California: Short Version, 1949-1950 (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 31)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Bank of America: Stockholders Trailer, 1948-1950, undated (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 32)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Benton, 1950, undated (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 33)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Bethlehem Steel, 1947, undated (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 34)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Bituminous Coal Industry: Legal, 1951 (Offsite-box 3924, Folder 35)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Bituminous Coal Industry: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1951 (Offsite-box R70)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Bituminous Coal Industry: Miscellaneous, 1950-1953 (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 1-2)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Bituminous Coal Industry: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1951 (Offsite-box R70)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Burlington Mills: Legal, 1950 (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 3)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Burlington Mills: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1950, undated (Offsite-box R70)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Burlington Mills: Miscellaneous, 1950-1951 (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 4)
- The March of Time: Commercial: B- Miscellaneous, 1945-1947 (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 5)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Campbell Soup, 1948-1950 (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 6)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Cancer Fund, 1945-1946 (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 7)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Cannon Mills [RESTRICTED], 1950 (Offsite-box R70)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Chesapeake and Ohio: Week-End at White Sulphur: Legal, 1948 (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 8)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Chesapeake and Ohio: Week-End at White Sulphur: Miscellaneous, 1948-1949 (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 9)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Chesterfield, 1940-1944, undate (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 10)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Chesterfield [RESTRICTED], 1939, undated (Offsite-box R70)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Chesterfield [RESTRICTED], 1939, undated (Offsite-box R40)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Chesterfield [RESTRICTED], 1939, undated (Offsite-box R41)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Chesterfield: Durham: Dopesheets and Key Numbers, 1939-1940 (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 11-14)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Chesterfield: Durham: Tobaccoland U.S.A., 1939-1943 (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 15-17)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Chesterfield: Durham [RESTRICTED], 1942 (Offsite-box R41)
- The March of Time: Commercial: China Relief, 1938, 1948 (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 18)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Chrysler, 1952-1953 (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 19)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Chrysler [RESTRICTED], 1952 (Offsite-box R41)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Citizens Committee for Eisenhower, 1952-1953, undated (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 20)
- The March of Time: Commercial: Cleveland Electric Company, 1947-1950 (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 21-22)